{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Must I finish all this work in an hour?. \" No, you ___.\"",
      "a": "must not",
      "b": "won't",
      "c": "should not",
      "d": "need not",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\nMust + S + O? \nNo, S + need not. \nRemember: \n- must not - prohibition (it is not allowed) \n- need not - option (it is not necessary)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "My sister never used to oppose me, but my brother occasionally ___.",
      "a": "did",
      "b": "used to",
      "c": "usedn't",
      "d": "didn't",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Used to (in the past) so we use \"did\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why didn't you answer when I called to you? \" I ___, but you didn't hear me\"",
      "a": "couldn't",
      "b": "didn't answer",
      "c": "did",
      "d": "had to",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Auxiliary verbs could be called helping verbs: they don't mean anything when they are alone, but when in a sentence, they help complete the form and meaning of main verbs. \n+The most common auxiliary verbs are: to be; to have , to do \n+Use an auxiliary verb when you want to avoid repeating some part of your sentence (because it can be deduced from the context) \n- Didn't, called (in the past) so we use \"\"did\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Paul lives in London, and so ___ his parents.",
      "a": "are",
      "b": "do",
      "c": "don't",
      "d": "live",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Auxiliary verbs could be called helping verbs: they don't mean anything when they are alone, but when in a sentence, they help complete the form and meaning of main verbs. \n+The most common auxiliary verbs are: to be;to have , to do \n+Use an auxiliary verb when you want to avoid repeating some part of your sentence (because it can be deduced from the context) \n- live (verb) so we use \"\"do\"\" \nRemember: \n- so do I/we/they/you \n- so does he/she/it",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She used to go shopping on Sundays, ___?",
      "a": "used she",
      "b": "didn't she",
      "c": "usedn't she to",
      "d": "did she",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Auxiliary verbs could be called helping verbs: they don't mean anything when they are alone, but when in a sentence, they help complete the form and meaning of main verbs. \n+The most common auxiliary verbs are: to be;to have , to do \n+Use an auxiliary verb when you want to avoid repeating some part of your sentence (because it can be deduced from the context) \n- Used to (in the past) so we use \"\"didn't she\"\" (question tag)\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Oh, Jane, you've broken still another glass. You ought ___ when you washed it.",
      "a": "be careful",
      "b": "to careful",
      "c": "to be careful",
      "d": "to have been careful",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Tense: Past Perfect \n- Structure: Ought + To Verb: Had-&gt; have",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is as poor as poor ___ be.",
      "a": "can",
      "b": "may",
      "c": "must",
      "d": "should",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Auxiliary verbs could be called helping verbs: they don't mean anything when they are alone, but when in a sentence, they help complete the form and meaning of main verbs. \n+The most common auxiliary verbs are: to be;to have , to do \n+Use an auxiliary verb when you want to avoid repeating some part of your sentence (because it can be deduced from the context) \nRemember: \n- as .... as .... can be\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will the weather clear up this afternoon? \"No, I'm afraid it ___ \"",
      "a": "may not",
      "b": "won't",
      "c": "mustn't",
      "d": "shouldn't",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Auxiliary verbs could be called helping verbs: they don't mean anything when they are alone, but when in a sentence, they help complete the form and meaning of main verbs. \n+The most common auxiliary verbs are: to be;to have , to do \n+Use an auxiliary verb when you want to avoid repeating some part of your sentence (because it can be deduced from the context) \n- Will -&gt; Won't",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I ___ the book, but I hardly remember it.",
      "a": "can read",
      "b": "may read",
      "c": "can have read",
      "d": "may have read",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Tense: Present perfect \n- Structure: May/could...+ have +PP",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "You might ___ advise me to give up my fortune as spend it in gambling.",
      "a": "as good",
      "b": "as well",
      "c": "well",
      "d": "as well as",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Might as well .... as: a phrase indicating that it is probably better to do something than not to do it",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}